{"data":[{"question":"As he drank, he held the saucer in one hand and the ______ in the other.","a":"cup tea","b":"tea cup","c":"tea's cup","d":"cup's tea","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"The ______ is open.","a":"door garage","b":"garage door","c":"door's garage","d":"garage's door","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"My mother bought some shoes at the ______.","a":"shop of shoes","b":"shoes' shop","c":"shoe-shop","d":"shop-shoes","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I love having a nice ______.","a":"coffee morning","b":"morning coffee","c":"morning's coffee","d":"coffee's morning","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"It was a nice ______.","a":"chocolate cake","b":"cake chocolate","c":"cake's chocolated","d":"chocalate's cake","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I am going to do some ______.","a":"wind surfing","b":"surf winding","c":"surfing wind","d":"wind surf","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I like that yellow ______.","a":"lamp table","b":"table lamp","c":"table's lamp","d":"lamp's table","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They sat on a ______.","a":"wood bench","b":"bench wood","c":"wooden bench","d":"wood's bench","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adjectives are words that are used to describe a noun \n+ Structure: Adj + Noun \n+ wood (n) - wooden (adj)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"They lived in a ______.","a":"stone's house","b":"stone house","c":"house's stone","d":"house stone","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"We say 'a glass or wine' when it's full. When it's empty we say ______.","a":"a wine glass","b":"a glass wine","c":"a wine's glass","d":"a glass' wine","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Sometimes we use a noun to describe another noun. In that case, the first noun \"acts as\" an adjective: \n+The \"noun as adjective\" always comes first and in singular form \n+ Structure: two separate words (car door); two hyphenated words (book-case); one word (bathroom) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"61","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}